[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Captain Tupolev, played by Stellan Skarsgard in the movie The Hunt for Red October, is commander of what Soviet submarine?", "correct_answer": "Kanavelov", "incorrect_answers": ["Andropov", "Gringov", "Grishin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alongside what American actor did Leonardo DiCaprio star in the movie Whats Eating Gilbert Grape?", "correct_answer": "Johnny Depp", "incorrect_answers": ["John Travolta", "Tom Cruise", "Keanu Reeves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About how many years have beagles been around?", "correct_answer": "2,000", "incorrect_answers": ["5,000", "4,000", "3,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which are the four tastes considered as basic in Western culture?", "correct_answer": "Bitter, sweet, sour and salty", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweet, salty, tasteless, and sour", "Bitter, salty, sweet, and savory", "Sweet, salty, chilly, and sour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did British film maker Alfred Hitchcock pass away?", "correct_answer": "1980", "incorrect_answers": ["1977", "1975", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By what nickname was shipping magnate Onasis better known?", "correct_answer": "Ari", "incorrect_answers": ["Psi", "Soc", "Uri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The car in which John Kennedy was riding when he was killed had a bubble top that was not used.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for 1984?", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone for Rhinestone", "incorrect_answers": ["Jerry Lewis for Slapstick of Another Kind", "Peter OToole for Supergirl", "Burt Reynolds for Cannonball Run II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Darth Vader is Luke Skywalkers father.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a breed of pig?", "correct_answer": "Ridgeback", "incorrect_answers": ["Norwegian Yorkshire", "Vietnamese pot-belly", "Tokyo-X"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about parasites in general?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They are usually much smaller that their host.", "They are highly specialized organisms.", "They reproduce faster than their host and in much larger quantities."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is considered the worlds first photojournalist?", "correct_answer": "Jacob Riis", "incorrect_answers": ["Eadweard Muybridge", "Matthew  Brady", "Minor White"]}]